So, like week 18, what's it what's it
feel like as you guys get ready for
wrestling?
Um
really just a week we trying to get
ourselves together for prep. Um making
sure we finishing off the right way. Um
and just having a good time with each
other, you know, having memories from
this past year.
>> Are you in a sort of reflection period
yet on the year or are you still just
sort of focusing on Cleveland and then
you'll get there sort of when you get
there?
>> Not yet. Really after the game.
You had that touchdown on the screen
against Arizona. You've always been good
at at that kind of stuff, but do you
feel like the screen game is an area
where you've improved, taking another
step this season?
>> Uh, yeah, I would say so. Yeah, overall
just getting the ones behind the line of
scrimmages, making them work with no
blockers. Yeah, I would say so. Yeah.
>> Where do you think you've improved this
year, Jamar?
Um, I feel like this exactly what Hobby
asked me the other day, but it's hard to
it's hard to say. You know what I'm
saying? Coming from the season I had
last year, trying to capitalize off
that. Um,
I'm really just trying to be more
consistent. It's It's not really what
I'm getting better at or what I'm best
at. It's really just maintaining
consistency throughout the year.
>> There was the the touchdown drought for
whatever you want to say it. Like, how
crazy are the coverages teams are
throwing at you in the red zones? In the
red zone. Um, majority of the time it's
just like
man doubled with some combos. Um, and
sometimes it's some stuff I don't
normally see. You know what I'm saying?
Sometimes it confuses me a little bit,
but a lot of times defenses scheme up
for situations like that.
>> What What have you learned about Burrow
this year that maybe you didn't? Is
there anything new that you gained this
year that maybe from previous years?
>> Um,
nothing really. I feel like he's been
more social this year, more outspoken
and more than any year.
>> Why Why do you think that that might be?
>> Uh I'm not sure. I think he's finally
comfortable a little bit, but then
again, he's been here for a while. So,
uh I don't know. I want to say he's
getting comfortable.
>> What kind of impact does it have on the
team when when your quarterback is, you
know, when he's that more mallet spoken,
he's more vocal, speaks up more. What
kind of impact does that have on the
rest of you?
Uh, I feel like he's always been that
type of guy, you know, especially coming
in as a rookie. Um, and in my second
year, too. So,
um, I feel like he's been the same guy
overall since I since I got here. Well,
since I've met him, you know what I'm
saying? Um, but he he always keeps
improving every year, always ready to
work when it's time to work. You know,
he has an on and off switch. Um, so he's
always been the same person since I met
him.
>> Who on the team do you feel like has
improved the most this season?
>> DJ Turner. 100%.
>> You face elite corners every day. What
stands out about DJ?
>> Um, I think the most this year that's
that caught my eye the most this year
about DJ is just
>> him switching his techniques from press
to off and physical to just feet. I
think that's the biggest thing from this
year.
>> When you have a duo of Dax and DJ as a
receiver, how tough is it knowing either
side? You got a tough matchup.
>> Um, it's just like playing offense. You
know what I'm saying? DB's trying to
stop us. is just picking your poison at
the end of the day. You know, you got to
find a receiver that you like and
hopefully make a play.
>> We talked to you after the uh game last
week and told you you need 11 catches to
break your own franchise record for most
of the season. You said right then
that's not going to happen. You're not
going to do it. Have you changed your
mind?
>> I don't know. I mean like I'm Have I
ever had 11 10 catches on Cleveland?
>> No.
>> Okay. Well, now I'm gonna try to do it
now. there. So, good to know.
>> So, you're saying
>> it's possible?
>> Possible.
>> It's always possible. Anything's
possible.
>> What is is this the best the offensive
line has played since you've been in the
league?
>> Uh, I would say so. Yeah. I don't know
what the stats say, like how many sacks
he took from the past previous years,
but I would say so. Yeah. How do you um
why do you think that is? Is it is it is
it the guys? Is it how they're playing
or what is it? What do you think it is?
>> Uh could be the guys up front. You know,
they definitely do a great job. I can
say that. I watched it. Um Green Bay
game, Ra first Ravens game. Those guys
did a good job of handling Bliss's
picking up and and just handing off the
different techniques that that they get.
>> What do you rank Denzel in terms of
course in the league guys you face? How
how good is he compared to maybe the
other guys?
>> Um I just rank him first just because
that's the only only person that I see
in a division that's you know one of the
top guys for sure.
>> What makes him so good at what he does?
>> Um I just think he's just really
patient. You know he he's really patient
as a DB and you know he got good feet.
>> You and Joe talk about um we got to
start making these years count. Like
we're playing really well. We're playing
as well as we thought we would. Well, in
the pros, we've got to start getting
more out of these years as a team. Does
that conversation ever come up with you
guys?
>> No, you can't have a You don't have
conversations like that. They don't like
it don't matter if I put all my all into
it and Joe pushes all we still got 11,
10, nine other people we got to worry
about. So, you it don't really matter if
we both putting our all into the season.
That's like me having a triple crown
season like last year. We don't go
nowhere. So, it don't really matter.
It's still a team effort.
>> Is that how how have you guys how was
that? How have you handled that? I
should say, you know, given you you max
out everything you can, it's still team
doesn't have the success you'd like.
>> I can't I can't do nothing but continue
to be who I can who I could be. I got to
control the things that I can control. I
can't control what people do and how
they make plays on the field.
>> Do you feel like this group is close? I
mean, you've seen what the offense has
done here the last couple of weeks. Do
you feel like you're getting close?
>> Um, I feel like that's the same question
I get asked every year. Are we close?
You know, I say the same thing every
year. I don't I mean at this point I'm
we going to keep battling and that's all
we can do as players and control intro
and make plays and opportunities when
our numbers call. That's all we can do.
>> Joe said yesterday something's got to
change and I think he's been adamant
about that. I think you've talked about
a little bit. What needs to be the thing
that changes the most to get y'all from
stop being close to finally getting
there? Um, I think I think some of the
things are pretty obvious what we need
to change, but at the end of the day, I
I can't really say or put an emphasis on
what needs to be changed because that's
not my role, but it's pretty obvious on
what some issues need to be changed,
though.
>> Is that is it fixable in an offseason?
The things we're seeing,
>> it's 100% fixable. I believe so.
>> Sorry, just one more. Mark, if you don't
mind,
>> you know, a lot of guys have talked
about the importance of of winning this
week and and it feels like a lot of the
guys are bought into winning. Why is we
understand as football players, it's
fundamental what you do. Why is it
important to win this game Sunday?
>> Um, just going out with a win for the
organization. At the end of that, we
didn't have the best year. I feel like
going out with a L just won't be good
for us going into the offseason. Um,
just overall an experience. You want to
win your last game going out if if
you're a football player period. I feel
like knowing that you might not know
it's your last game, but you you want to
win.
>> Thanks.
>> Thanks, Mark. Thanks, Mark.
>> Appreciate that.
>> Way to work, man. Appreciate it.